Dear Friends In This Video Let Us Discuss
About 19 Stocks Including Escorts
ICICL Lombard TVS
Motors Exeta Dos Have Announced
Bonus Or Stock Split Or
Dividend Welcome To Stock Info
Media I Am Namboothiri Please Like Share
And
Subscribe Excel Industries Current
Market Price Is Rs. 882 Per
Share Company Announced A Board Meeting
On 24 April
2024 Purpose Of The Board Meeting Is
Declaring Dividend And Announcing Annual
Result Escorts Kuborto
Limited Current Market Price Is Rs.
3100 Per Share Company Announced A
Board Meeting On 9 May
2024 Purpose Of The Board Meeting Is
Declaring Dividend and Announcing Annual
Result
ICICI Lombard General Insurance Current
Market Price is 1000
per share Company announced a dividend of Rs. 6 per
share Both the
ex-dividend date and record
date is not at all
finalized Anoop Engineering Current
Market Price is Rs.
333 per
share Company announced a stock bonus
in ratio one is one that means if you have ten
shares of Anoop
Engineering you will get another ten
shares as bonus Both the ex-bonus
date and record date is 23
April 2024
Good Luck India Limited Current
Price is Rs.
925 per share Company announced a dividend
of Rs. 20 per  This share both the
ex date and record date is not at all
finalized
Deepna Farm Chem Limited this penny stock with
current price of Rs
910 is announced a boat meeting on
26 April
2024 Purpose of the boat meeting is
stock split and announcing
bonus Electron Engineering Company
Limited current market price is
Rs
1182 per share Company announced a dividend of Rs 2 per
share and announced a
stock split in ratio one is two that means if you have
10 shares
of Electron Engineering you will get Rs 2
dividend for each and every
share and your ten shares convert to
20 shares both the ex date and
record  Date is not
finalized at all 360 One Warm Limited Current
Market Price is Rs
998 The company announced a board meeting
on 23 April
2024 Purpose of the board meeting is
declaring dividend and announcing annual
result
Agrotech Foods Limited Current
Market Price is Rs 719 per
share The company announced a board meeting
on 24 April
2024 Purpose is same declaring
dividend and announcing annual result
Aditya Birla Sun Life Limited
Share is trading around Rs 502 This
company also announced a board
meeting on 26 April
2024 Purpose is declaring dividend
and  Announcing Q
for PST Tillers Tractors
Limited Current Market Price is
Rs
3373 per share Company announced a board
meeting on 26 April
2024 Purpose of the board meeting is
declaring dividend and announcing Q
for Swaraj Engines Limited
Shares around Rs
2434 per share Company announced dividend
of Rs 95 per share Both ex
date and record date is not at all
finalized MS Financial Services
Current Market Price is Rs
288 per share Company announced a board
meeting on 24 April 2024 Purpose of
the board meeting of MS Financial
Services is declaring dividend and
announcing Q
for Aster DM  Healthcare Limited
Current Market Price is
1688 per share The company announced huge
dividend of Rs 118 per share and
every share you held on the record
date that is 23 April
2024 DCB Bank Current Market
Price is Rs 121 per share The company
announced a board meeting on
April 2024 Purpose of the board
meeting is Q4 and
dividend Sanofi India Limited Current
Market Price is Rs
8265 per share The company announced a dividend of Rs
117 per share both the
ex date and record date is
3rd May 2024
TVS Motors Current Market
Price is Rs
2100 Company announced stock bonus in
Ratio 41 that
means if you have 10 shares of
TVS Motors you are eligible to get
40 shares as bonus so you will
have 50 shares both x bonus date
and record date is not at all
finalized by the company if the company
final the x bonus date and record date
definitely we will inform you through
this channel as early as possible
Advertising Limited Current Price is Rs
810 Company announced a bonus and
stock split record it is not at all finalized Rs
57328 crore order book This multi-bagger
civil construction company receives new
order worth Rs
2323 from BHEL and JSOL
The name of the company is Power Mech
Projects Limited The company has
Secured orders with Rs
2323 crores The biggest order of
Rs
12289 crores is from Bharat Heavy
Electricals Limited The other two
orders are from Jintal Steel Odisha
Limited for Rs
5640 crores and Rs
5274 crores Thank you for watching my
video Please Like Share and Subscribe